Andi Sultan Asharil Raphi

Balikpapan, East Kalimantan, Indonesia



andiaril186@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/andi-sultan-asharilraphi-2a77b3150



0895347047819



https://github.com/andisltn48

Summary

I am a graduate of the Kalimantan Institute of Technology majoring in Informatics. I am currently focusing as a Backend Developer. I have some experience with the technology needed in Backend development. I also have experience in creating REST APIs. I'm interested in working as a Backend Developer

Experience

Web Programmer

Inotive Technology

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022 (4 months)

Back End Developer

PT. Bantubantuin

Jun 2022 - Sep 2022 (4 months)

As a Back End Developer

in creating a Rest API to be used in webstite or mobile-based Bantubantuin applications using Laravel framework.

Backend Developer

PT. MEDIA KREASI ABADI

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022 (6 months)

Participate in Kampus Merdeka internship activities at PT. Media Kreasi Abadi. In this internship I work as a Backend Developer making Rest API using Nest JS.

🎍 Full Stack Developer

Institut Teknologi Kalimantan

Oct 2021 - Jun 2022 (9 months)

As a full stack developer in developing web inventory management information system for the purposes of the final project. A web-based application to perform inventory data management at the Kalimantan Institute of Technology



Full Stack Engineer

Freelance

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022 (3 months)

Develop a website-based application for pet shop purposes using the Laravel framework

Full Stack Developer

Freelance

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022 (3 months)

Worked as a full stack developer in developing WEBARSITEK, a web-based application created using the Laravel framework used for design ordering architect.

Back End Developer

Institut Teknologi Kalimantan

Jun 2021 - Sep 2021 (4 months)

As a back end developer in developing the H2H Mandiri Management Information System, a host information system 2 hosts Bank Mandiri at the Kalimantan Institute of Technology created with using the Laravel framework.

Full Stack Engineer

Freelance

May 2021 - Jul 2021 (3 months)

Develop a website-based application for running events using the Laravel framework.

Material Lecturer

Institut Teknologi Kalimantan

Oct 2020 - Jan 2021 (4 months)

Teach in Algorithm & Programming 1 practicum class using Python programming language.

Assistant Lecturer

Institut Teknologi Kalimantan

Feb 2020 - Jun 2020 (5 months)

Teach in Algorithm & Programming 1 practicum class using Python programming language.

Education

Bachelor's degree, Informatics

2018 - 2022

SMKN 6 Balikpapan

2015 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications



Skills

Postman API • Python (Programming Language) • NestJS • Node.js • Trello • JavaScript • Laravel • PHP • HTML • Bootstrap